follownews.com 2011-06-23

# follownews.com Terms of Service And Privacy Policy

| **Privacy Policy and Terms of Use

* * *

**  
---  
**Privacy Policy**  
  
Privacy issues are a high priority for us at follownews and we follow standard industry practices to maintain your personal information. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

 **follownews** does not spam or sell/lease its user information to third parties.  
  
****

**Policy Coverage**  
  
This Privacy Policy covers follownews's treatment of personally identifiable information that follownews collects when you are on the follownews site, and when you use follownews's services. This policy also covers follownews's treatment of any personally identifiable information that follownews's business partners share with follownews. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that follownews does not own or control, or to people that follownews does not employ or manage.  
  
**Cookies**  
follownews (or third party service providers on our behalf) may set and access cookies on your computer. A cookie is a small amount of data (often including a unique identifier), that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. follownews uses cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our site.  

We may use cookies, IP address and browser data to control the display of ads, to deliver editorial content, and to personalize information. Our cookies may contain personally identifiable information.

Some of our advertisers may serve you cookies as well. We do not have control over cookies placed by advertisers. If you don't want cookies, most Web browsers include an option that allows you to not accept them. If you set your browser to refuse cookies, some portions of our sites may not function efficiently.  
  
****

**Use of Information by follownews**  
  
follownews is an online website that offers a variety of services designed to connect people from around the world. The information, whether personal information of any form of self-expression is used to help you describe yourself to other users. follownews also collects additional information in order to operate and improve our service. follownews, is the sole owner of the information collected on the follownews site.

 **VISIBILITY OF PUBLIC CREATIVE CONTRIBUTIONS:** In addition to being a social and professional networking site, follownews also provides a variety of forums for its members to express themselves in the form of articles, columns, opinions, comments, reviews, art and photographs. Since this expression is linked to the member's identity and the expression is in the public domain, the compilation of a member's creative contributions to follownews will be visible to all visitors of follownews whether or not they are registered members of follownews.

 **EMAIL COMMUNICATIONS:** follownews generally communicates with you as a registered member of follownews through the primary email that you have specified at the time of registration. This is also used as the login text string in conjunction with the password to authenticate you on the follownews site. Your email and password are never shared with anybody within or outside follownews. follownews uses this email address to send you three types of communications:

  * Sending you emails related to the proper functioning of your account (e.g. when you receive a response to a classified you have posted on follownews or when you receive an invitation to join the personal network of another person)
  * Sending you newsletters that you have subscribed to
  * Sending you occasional announcements about changes in follownews's policies or promotions introduction of new services
  * Please note that these email communications may contain commercial messages of advertisers; however, follownews does not provide your personal information or emails to any of the advertisers; we just include the advertising banners they provide us in the emails that we send. As always you can opt out of the newsletters or promotional announcements.

****

**Other Terms of Use**  
  
****

**Policy on Abuse on follownews**  
  
follownews is committed to ensuring and enforcing a safe and friendly online community space for all our members. To this effect, we have come up with a Policy on Abuse that we would like all our members to be aware of. These rules govern the use of the follownews.com website and its product/service offerings and we would like all our members to cooperate in complying with these rules so that everyone can have a pleasant experience.

 **Conduct and use of language:**

  * Member contributions must be civil and tasteful and must not be malicious or designed to offend. Use of swear-words or profanity is strictly prohibited.
  * Do not refer to the personality of other participants or attack an individual's character or personally insult another member. Do not use the Network to harass, threaten or verbally abuse or intimidate anyone, or behave in any manner that would cause annoyance or distress to other members.
  * Do not to post any material that is obscene, defamatory, profane, libelous, threatening, harassing, abusive, hateful or embarrassing towards other person(s) or an entity. We encourage a healthy exchange of opinions and disagreements. By all means challenge an opinion â€“ but please do it respectfully. Name-calling, insults and use of foul or abusive language will not be tolerated. This includes the use of offensive member Display Names and URLs (your personal website address on follownews). 
  * Please be sure before you divulge the details of your identity or personal information in your post(s), including photos of yourself or your family and friends. Anything posted online is accessible to the entire internet community and follownews.com is not liable in cases where such information is misused. Please be aware of the general dangers of online information sharing like identity theft, phishing and other fraudulent activites.
  * Members of follownews.com are not permitted to collect or distribute personal data concerning other members at any time. 
  * Do not post messages more than once. This is also known as flooding. follownews.com reserves right to delete such posts and may terminate the accounts of such members.
  * A member of follownews.com must not impersonate another member.

****

**Changes to Privacy Policy and Notice**  
  
follownews may change this policy from time to time in its discretion. Your continued use of our sites indicates your consent to this privacy policy and any amended versions of it. This policy was last updated on October 8th, 2008.
